http://www.vt.edu/about/privacy.html

Research
Current page:
Privacy Statement
ready1
Privacy Statement
Virginia Tech has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web page: www.vt.edu.
Information Automatically Logged
The server collects the IP address, date, time, page accessed, browser type, and the referring page if present. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web page. The date and time are used to track the load on the server and peak usage times. We record the browser type to monitor market penetration of various web browsers so we can better determine what Internet technologies we may utilize in the design of our pages. We use page referrer data--that is, information about the web page that pointed you to our page--to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the web. These data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources.
Logging of Link Traversal
The Virginia Tech website logs all clicks on links within pages in order to assist us in determining the popularity of content and the various navigation methods used to find information. No personally identifiable information is recorded; only the time and date, and the links used.
Use of Cookies
The Virginia Tech home page issues and reads cookies to track any customization options you may have selected. These include what links were activated during a user's time on a website.
Personal Information
This Web page does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
Links to Virginia Tech Pages
This site contains links to other Virginia Tech pages. The privacy practices of other pages may vary with the purposes of the page. Consult the privacy statement on each page.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Virginia Tech is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location. User and password information, if requested, is encrypted before it is transmitted across the network.
Users should also consult Virginia Tech's policy on Acceptable Use. (PDF) Virginia Tech complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: askvt@vt.edu.
